<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[The Product Line]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[The Product Line]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/product-the-novel/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2015 03:10:47 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/product-the-novel/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Product by Ian S. McCain- a Novel Review]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Product by Ian S. McCain- a Novel Review</h1><p>I can say that within just a couple of paragraphs into this clever tale by Ian S. McCain, I was quite confident I was going to enjoy the entire thing. McCain's clever manipulation of language and page formatting demonstrates courageous writing, made all the better by a noticeable lack of blatant errors often found amongst similar endeavors.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://yakmax.com/product-by-ian-s-mccain-a-novel-review/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b28d0eb0-ca85-4e66-880a-c2a2d7e4365d</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2015 02:59:30 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Product (a novel) Book Trailer]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Product (a novel) Book Trailer</h1><p>Get your Copy on Amazon.com: http://amzn.to/18L0zRT 4.9 star review on Amazon.com 4.87star review on Goodreads.com Ernie Chase isn't just one of the infected. He's one of their runners. His job is simple; get the product to the other infected and keep the killing off the streets.</p><img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/i-LI0cdPui0/hqdefault.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=i-LI0cdPui0</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ac1fbbac-125b-4686-acfc-a28fe16ad0a2</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2015 02:58:25 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Book Review: Product by Ian McCain]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Book Review: Product by Ian McCain</h1><p>Fifty-year-old Ernie Chase is a liquor-soaked husk living on the streets of New York City. When Ernie is shot while witnessing a back alley drug deal, he believes that his miserable life is over. But he awakens, healthy, sober and youthful, handcuffed to a military cot in an abandoned hospital.</p><img src="http://iabookreviews.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/08/81velks+kwL._SL1500_-198x300.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://iabookreviews.com/book-review-product-by-ian-mccain/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">bb6d2cae-1b6f-4050-9303-e32ee5494c40</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2015 02:58:08 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ian S McCain]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Ian S McCain</h1><p>Check out this GoDaddy hosted webpage! http://iansmccain.com.</p><img src="http://cache.nebula.phx3.secureserver.net/obj/NzE4RjA4NTZBMUQzMEE2NkM2NEI6ODc2YjExYmU2ZWE5MWI5MDU2NTRmNWYyNmVmZWUxNjE="></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://iansmccain.com/#</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b73d7d15-e7ca-4e15-9114-3ca0e2278b28</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2015 02:47:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Product by Ian S. McCain]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Product by Ian S. McCain</h1><p>Ernie Chase is an alcoholic bum living on the streets of New York City. All he is worried about is finding his next drink and hiding from his daughter, Marie. Being a good daughter, Marie wanders the streets and volunteers at shelters continuously looking for her father.</p><img src="http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/41RrF1n6RBL._SL160_.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://bittenbybooks.com/product-by-ian-s-mccain/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9f5d4a0a-52b4-44f8-ae33-443d91c05096</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2015 03:09:54 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Product by Ian S. McCain Posted by: Jkrowyn  in Horror, Paranormal, Reviews September 30, 2013 Comments Off 1,365 Views  Ernie Chase is an alcoholic bum living on the streets of New York City. All he is worried about is finding his next drink and hiding from his daughter, Marie. Being a good daughter, Marie wanders the streets and volunteers at shelters continuously looking for her father. He used to be a good man and she just wants her father clean, warm and sober. Ernie’s life has just about reached an all-time low. He breaks into a church and drinks the vicar’s liquor. As he is laying in his box in some back alley, he winds up in the middle of what some gangsters think is a drug deal, but actually is much worse. Ernie ends up shot and blacks out. When he comes to, he is handcuffed to a cot in an abandoned hospital. Not only is he still alive, he now looks like a model in his early twenties. He feels no aches and his missing teeth are back in his mouth. A man named Gideon is by his bed telling him he has been infected with a virus, and the only treatment for it is receiving blood. Gideon teaches Ernie how to inject blood directly into his vein through a needle. He also finds out that he now has to work for Gideon for the rest of his life or die. There are more infected in the city, and Gideon provides the product for these infected. Ernie’s new job is delivering this product to other infected and procuring humans for the farm where they make this product. To avoid notice usually only the homeless, gangsters or criminals are gathered. A year goes by with no trouble for Ernie, and then one evening he notices there are new infected in the city. They seem organized and Ernie grows curious. He wants more answers about himself and this virus. He grows sloppy during a routine gathering of new gangsters and things quickly get out of control. He knows he has to be careful because Gideon can still hold Marie’s health over his head, but he will get his answers. Product is a dark, completely new take on the vampire. Ian McCain writes a superb story, giving us a complete history for his vampires, fleshing them out and making the reader care about what happens. They can have a conscious and care for others, and they can also be ruthless killers who do not give a damn. The fight scenes are vividly written and violent, and I could totally picture them happening. I did not see the ending coming and I want to rush out and read book two, Byproduct, right away. Book Stats:</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/product-the-novel/product-by-ian-s-mccain-posted-by-jkrowyn-in-horror-para/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">92528979-7fac-4644-9c9d-3ee6094ca0c6</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2015 03:08:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Red City Review | Product by Ian McCain]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Red City Review | Product by Ian McCain</h1><p>At the beginning of the novel, Product, by Ian McCain, Ernie Chase is a decrepit and decaying man whose alcoholism has led him to a dilapidated life on the streets, where his thoughts wonder in vague directions as he stumbles from place to place.</p><img src="http://redcityreview.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/RCR-new-header2.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://redcityreview.com/reviews/product-by-ian-mccain/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0d30c1ed-0f3d-4c9f-828c-e9b4d6338498</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2015 02:55:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/41Ah9J6HxFL._BO2,204,203,200_PIsitb-sticker-v3-big,TopRight,0,-55_SX324_SY324_PIkin4,BottomRight,1,22_AA346_SH20_OU02_.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/product-the-novel/c535dc46-cdfa-40e3-b9b4-e16a848741f8/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c535dc46-cdfa-40e3-b9b4-e16a848741f8</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2015 02:54:54 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Product]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Product</h1><p>Ernie was just another homeless boozer spiraling toward self-destruction on New York City's deadly streets until the night he contracted a mysterious virus. It spread through his sickly body increasing his strength, speed and resilience, making him nearly immortal. However, such power come with a price.</p><img src="http://portlandbookreview.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/WhiteMansProblems-200x250.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://portlandbookreview.com/2013/08/product/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7ef90c3c-2c10-49e1-a7ef-041404905fff</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2015 02:54:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clarice's Book Nook: Product by Ian McCain]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Clarice's Book Nook: Product by Ian McCain</h1><p>H e can't remember what happy feels like. He has been a bum for a while now, living on the streets, getting booze however he can. Ernie is dying, slowly. But he knows this. His lifestyle choices are slowly killing him.</p><img src="http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/41Ah9J6HxFL._BO2,204,203,200_PIsitb-sticker-arrow-click,TopRight,35,-76_AA278_PIkin4,BottomRight,-69,22_AA300_SH20_OU01_.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://claricesbooknook.blogspot.com/2013/09/product-by-ian-mccain.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">955ff642-f714-4e14-97ea-2405190a9a6d</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2015 03:01:23 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>